-= 老友影迷公社 http://site.douban.com/fmc =-
本字幕由深圳老友影迷公社字幕组翻译 仅限交流使用 严禁用于商业用途
翻译：翼落凝羽 AnnaLynna 校对:海风
I mean, it's pretty dumb, but whatever.
确实有些傻帽，但是无所谓啦
Look at this.
快看
Oh, my God,that's so pretty.
偶的神呐，好美
I love it. Thank you so much, Aunt Nicole.
爱死了，妮可阿姨谢谢你
Isn't it pretty, Brit?
确实很美
Dad? More decaf?
老爸？要加多一些咖啡么？
(Aunt) So, you two. High school.That's pretty great.
你们俩现在可是高中生啦，不错哟
I guess. It's gonna be sorta weird though.
还好吧，但我觉得有点怪怪的
(Lynn)Really?
怪？
Our school is kind of a feeder for New Trier's
新里特尔的就像是我们学校的收容所
so we're gonna know like a ton of people already.
应该会有很多熟悉面孔
(Peter)Here, Annie.
安妮，拿着
Happy Birthday!
生日快乐！
It's like the one you saw on The Hills, right?
这个跟你在《好莱坞女孩》看到的差不多吧？
(Lynn) I don't think The Hills are the role models we were looking for.
我们可不是《好莱坞女孩》的粉丝
It's a bit revealing, don't you think?
你不觉得有点忒暴露了么？
She's fourteen,you guys.
拜托，她才14岁
Yeah, no need to remind me.
这个我知道
- So. You did great.- Mmm hmm!
哇，你真棒 嗯
Come on.
快点
Come on what?
干嘛？
Give it to me.[all chuckle]
送我的礼物呢？
(Lynn) What's she talking about?
她说什么？
It's a heavy box.[all chuckle]
这盒子很重
It's the new MacBook Pro.
这可是新版苹果笔记本
It's got a four gigabyte hard drive
有4G的硬盘
2.53 gigahertz proc--
处理器2.53G的
What? I know what that means.
笑什么笑？这个我在行
(Will) I think you're actually passing wind at this point.
这张你是正在放气吧
Daddy.
爸爸
it's getting late, Banannie.
不早了，宝贝儿
Five more minutes, Dad, please? It's still my birthday.
就5分钟好么？我生日还没过完哦
All right.11:15.
好吧      11:15
Promise.
我保证
Who are you talking to?
你在跟说话呢？
I'm chatting, Dad.
老爸 我在聊天
My friend Charlie from California.
我认识了一个加利福利亚的朋友，叫查理
He's a junior and plays volleyball for his high school.
他读高中，是他们学校排球队的
Ooh, a junior. Well, he's obviously a very smart kid.
哟，初中生哦 这孩子肯定相当聪明
LOL. Laugh out loud. Right?
LOL，是大笑的意思对吧？
Nice one, Dad.
行啊 老爸
PWOMS?
[chuckles] "Parent watching over my shoulder."
老爸在背后监视[聊天内容]
And what is that?
全是新词汇，这句又是什么意思？
"Laughing my ass off. Me too."
笑屁了,我也是
No, wait.
等等
Dad, can you go talk to Mom about mortgage payments or something.
老爸 你好像更应该去跟老妈商量下按揭付款之类的事吧？
All right. Good night,birthday girl.
好吧，晚安 小寿星
Good night.Love you.
晚安 爱你
Love you.
我也爱你
(Coach) All right.Let's see what you got.
来吧，秀出你们的实力
There you go, ladies.Touch the line.
美女们听好了，踩线
Make sure you're touching the line.
一定要确保踩到线
(Coach) Last one.You're almost there.
最后一个就快到了
[incoming message]
Hey, Annie, come here!
安妮，过来一下！
This is Serena.
这位是塞琳娜
So, you're Peter Cameron's little sister.
你就是彼得 卡梅隆的妹妹
Your brother's hot as shit.
你哥可真他妈帅毙了
Uh, thanks, I guess.
还好吧 替他谢谢你
(Serena) So, I'm having a little party at my house Saturday night
这个周六在我家举办个派对
and you, little Cameron, are invited.
你，小卡梅隆，欢迎来参加
Okay. Uh,thanks, Serena.
好啊 谢啦，塞琳娜
Tell your brother.
重点是把你哥带过来
(Will)ls it deliberate?
你故意的吧
NO, not at all.
当然不是
(Lynn)Hey, honey?
嗨 亲爱的？
No phones at the table, please.
拜托，饭桌上不要玩手机
Sorry.
不好意思
Katie, will you take a picture of me and Peter?
卡蒂，帮忙 替我跟彼得照张相
(Will)Hey, what did Mom just say?
喂，妈妈怎么说的？
I was just gonna send a photo to Charlie, but okay.
我正准备给查理发照片，等等
(Peter) So, seriously,what's this guy's deal?
说正经的，这个查理是什么人
Well, he's smart.And funny.
嗯，他很聪明，又幽默
His brother's being recruited by UC Berkeley for football
他哥哥在加州大学伯克利分校足球队
and that's where he wants to go, but for volleyball.
他也想去那里，但是去进排球队
Oh, right.The girl's sport.
哈，娘们的运动
(Will)What do his parents do?
他父母是做什么的呢
His mom teaches kids with autism
他老妈给自闭症孩子上课
and his dad works for ESPN.
他老爸在体育电视台工作
I don't know,sweetheart.
亲爱的，我纳闷了
Sounds like he's got too much going for him for my likin'.
这个家伙是不是太完美了
Hey.
你好
(Will over phone) Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
我知道你的意思
I'm looking at them right now.[phone ringing]
我正在浏览呢
These are definitely for a clothing company, right?
这些确实是服装公司吧
So why isn't anybody wearing a shirt?
怎么没一个人是穿着衣服的？
[chuckling] No, I'm kidding. Yeah.They're good. Go with it. Okay. Bye.
开玩笑的 很棒，继续加油 就这样，再见
Hi, Mom!
嗨 妈妈
(Lynn)Hey, honey, how'd it go?
嗨亲爱的，怎么样？
I made the team!
我入队了！
You did? That's great!
真的么，太棒了
What happened?
怎么了？
Annie?
安妮？
Come on.Where are you?
拜托，你去哪了？
(Annie)About time.
出现的刚刚好
Hi,Charlie
嗨，查理
Where's mine, bozo?[typing]
那你的照片呢，小笨蛋？
What?
什么？
"I'm really 20.Sophomore at UC Berkeley."
其实我20了，在伯克利读大二
What?
什么？
Twenty?
20？
Bye.
再见
Hello.
你好
Wow.
哇
(Serena) Hi, girls.So did your brother come with?
你们好，美女们 你们的哥哥也来了么？
No, he's packing for college.
没有，他要去读大学了，正在收拾行李
(Serena) Great.Looks like I wore these for nothing.
擦 白打扮了
Come join us.
一起玩呗
We're teaching Alexa how to give a blow job.
我们正在教亚莉克莎如何口交
She sucks. She keeps gagging.
她太逊了 才没几口就要呕
Serena, where's your bathroom?
塞琳娜, 你家洗手间在哪？
We have like six of them.Go down the hall. You'll find one.
这里有6间洗手间 大厅走到底就有一个
Hi, Dad.
嗨 老爸
Hey, sweetheart.You have a good time?
嗨 宝贝儿 玩的开心么？
Mm-hm.
嗯
Those girls kinda freaked me out though.
说实话，那些女孩有点恐怖
Yeah ?
哦？
I-l really want them to like me, you know?
但我确实想融入她们
It means a lot.
这很重要
Just be yourself
只需要做好你自己就好了
If the Serenas of the world don't like it, it's their loss.
如果塞琳娜她们的世界不欢迎你，那是她们的损失
No, it's high school, Dad.
老爸 这可是中学
If the Serenas of the world don't like me
如果塞琳娜们的世界不欢迎我
I'm screwed.You get it?
我就玩完了  懂么？
Not really, no.Sorry, I've, I've really gotta--
不能这么说 不好意思，我还要忙...
Yeah, okay.
哎，去吧
Night.
晚安
(Brit)ls that Charlie?
是查理么？
(Annie) Yeah, he has a big paper due tomorrow.
呃，他明天有个论文要交
That picture he sent you is so hot. He's totally ripped.
他给你发来的那张图片太帅了 他真他妈性感
Sh. Shut up.My mom.
嘘 别说了 我妈来了
I got donut holes.
我买了甜甜圈
They're very good. Here.
很美味 快尝尝
Who was that?
她们是谁啊？
- It was Serena and Tanya.  - Oh.
- 那是塞琳娜和塔尼亚         - 哦
Get anything good?
买了什么好东西？
Mm.
嗯
What?
是什么呀？
She told me to buy a bra.
她让我买个胸罩
Oh, really? Let me see.
真的？让我看看
Classy.
呃，豹纹哟
- You saved the receipt though, right?  - Mom.
- 收据还在吧？        - 妈
If you think you're ready for a bra like that
当你觉得这个适合你穿的时候，
then we'll talk about it, okay?
我们再来谈，好么？
(Brit) Serena kinda made fun of her sports bra.
塞琳娜总取笑她的运动胸衣
- Why? - 'Cause it totally, like, flattens out my boobs.
- 为什么？- 因为我穿着它，呃，就像个飞机场
She said that guys would think that I was hotter
她说要想让自己看起来更性感
if I, like, had a better bra.
我就得，呃，穿这个
Does, like, Serena say like all the time too?
塞琳娜是不是也总是说“呃”？
Because, like,you never used to.
因为，呃，你以前可不这么说话
Sorry.
对不起
You don't have to dumb yourself down for guys, like Serena.
你不需要刻意模仿像塞琳娜那样的人
You know that.
懂么
Maybe she thinks that's all she's got to offer.
可能她觉得她的外表就是一切
(Brit) Her parents own half of downtown Chicago. [horn honking]
她父母坐拥半个芝加哥
You get my point though, right?
但你懂我的意思，对吧
Yes, Lynn.
我懂了，琳恩
It's a parking lot,moron. Go around!
这是停车场，白痴 绕行！
Did you get my point?
你到底有没有听懂我的意思？
Yeah, Mom. I get it.[horn honking]
好了妈妈 我懂了
Oh, for the love of--
哦，谢天谢---
- Bite me! - Mom!
- 你大爷的！- 妈！
Yeah, I'm gonna get the steak sandwich, medium, with grilled onions.
嗯，我要一个牛排三明治，半熟，加洋葱
And can I get a side of chips, please?
还要来份烤土豆条，谢谢
Oh, I'm sorry, we don't--
不好意思，我们没有---
(Al)He means French fries.
他的意思是薯条
Twenty years here, he still can't say French fries.
20年过去了，还是连薯条都说不好
I'm gonna have the same thing,actually, except rare on the steak.
我要跟他一样的，但是牛排要全生的
And to drink,we'll have a bottle of--
饮料嘛，给我们来瓶--
Really?
真的？
'92 Rothschild.
罗斯柴尔德92
Fantastic selection.
超赞的搭配
(Will) So what are we celebrating?
我们是要庆祝什么？
(Al) So A & A wants to use us.For everything.
A&A一直都在利用我们
- They liked the campaign? - Liked?
- 他们喜欢上次的活动？- 上次？
How 'bout I just got a phone call from the CEO
我刚接了公司CEO电话
that was basically ten minutes of phone sex.
简直跟他妈10分钟电话缠绵似的
Hey, let me ask you something.
喂，我问你点事
How old are you?
你多大？
- Old enough.- Oh.
- 够大了      - 哦
I'm Claire, by the way.
顺便说下，我叫克莱儿，
Hi, Claire. I'm AI.
你好克莱儿，我是AI
- That's Will.  - Hi.
- 那家伙是威尔   - 你好
Please let me know if there's anything else you need.
你们还有其他什么需要呢？
Anything?
任何需要都能满足？
Can you stop? She's nineteen.
拜托你消停一会好么 她才19岁
One hour. That's all I ask.
一个小时，就一个小时
Just one hour with that ass.
就要她那美臀一小时
(Will)How's Barbara ?
芭芭拉怎么样了？
Oh, fuck off.
你妹的，滚远点
That is so weird.
太神奇了
Peter and I were just doing exactly the same thing in his room.
彼得跟我刚刚在他房间做了同一件事
(Annie) Ah, Dad.
哎哟，老爸
Okay. What now?
现在又要说什么？
What? How old are you?
什么？你到底多大？
[Annie, whispering] Why do you keep lying?
你干嘛总是撒谎？
What?
什么？
Why do you keep lying to me?
为什么你总对我说谎？
(Peter) Man, you won't believe the stuff I'm Finding in here.
老爹，你们都不会相信我在这里发现什么了
(Will) I'll say. You wanna keep these Playboys?
我猜，你想要把这些花花公子杂志收藏起来是吧？
What?
怎么可能？
Just kidding.
我开玩笑的
Oh. Yeah, me too.
哈，我也是
What, you packed em already?
你把他们都打包了？
Yeah, kinda.
恩，差不多是的
You all right with this?
你准备好了？
With What?
准备好什么？
The whole college thing.
去上大学
Yeah, I guess.
我猜是吧
Don't feel pressured
别给自己太大压力
into doing things you don't want to do.
去逼自己做不想做的事
Wait. This isn't another father-son talk, is it?
等等 你不是又要来一场父子间说教式的对话吧？
Oh, Dad, we had the sex talk, like, three years ago
老爸，我们三年前就开始谈性事了
and I still can't order a salad with cucumbers in it.
但是我都不曾自己点个黄瓜沙拉
I just don't want you to lose sight of what's important, like--
我只是不想让你失去重要的信念 -比如
Taking responsibility for my actions
为自己做的事情负责
living up to my potential and personal expectations
过自己期望的生活
staying true to my beliefs.Basically, being a man?
坚持自己的信仰 一句话，像个爷们？
Something like that.
差不多是这样
Relax, Pop.I got this. Trust me.
放心吧老爸 我都记得，相信你儿子吧
God. Come on.Let's hug it out.
哦 天，来拥抱下
[chuckles]
I feel the same way.
我也有这种感觉
You coming in, sweetheart? It's getting cold.
进来呀宝贝儿外面很冷
Hold on a sec.
等一下
Um, I'm talking to Brittany, Dad.
嗯，我在跟布兰特妮聊天
Two minutes.
2分钟
Okay. Now go away.
好啦，你先去吧
Hi.
你好
How do I know that?
我怎么知道是真的假的？
Okay.
好吧
Well, are you still a virgin?
那么，你还是处男？
Good, 'cause that would have been creepy.
那就好，要不也忒吓人了
So, um, how old were you when you--?
那么，嗯，你第一次是多大 --
Did you set the alarm?
订闹铃了没？
Force Held activated.
已经订了
Is Annie upstairs?
安妮在楼上么？
She's in her room. Peter's still out.
她在房间 彼得还没回来
Amen to that.
那就好
You heartless witch.
你这个冷血巫婆
What?
你说什么？
You're happy he's going, aren't you?
他要走 你窃喜吧？
Two words for you. Home gym.
送你四个字："运动健身”
His room's gonna look great with a treadmill in it.
安上跑步机后，他的房间会超赞的
Our poor kid is barely packed and you're already redecorating.
孩子还没收拾行李，你就合计重新装修房间
What can I say? Except--good riddance!
怎么说呢，简直就是解脱！
Fuck.
擦
Oh, for God's--
注意你的--
(Annie)They're in their room.
他们在房间里
Right now? Just a T-shirt and some underwear.
现在？只穿了一件衬衫和内衣？
No. With just the T-shirt.
错，连内衣都没穿
Okay.
好吧
Okay, it's dark now.
Ok，灯关了
[chuckles softly] Oh, I guess. What is it?
嗯，那是什么？
No.
别
Okay.
好吧
Is that everything?
就这样？
Yeah.
嗯
Katie, come give me a hug.
卡蒂，来抱一下
(Kate) No.I don't want you to go.
不 我不让你走
So, I guess I'm gonna go to college now.
那我现在就该出发了
I love you. Email me, okay?
我爱你 记得给我发邮件
Okay. Hey, and check my tweets.
我会的，要读我的 “围脖”哦
(Will)Okay, we gotta go, guys.
好的 我们走啦
(Will)We'll see you later.
再见
(Lynn) Bye. Bye, angel. Bye.
再见了小天使
[guide explaining,bells tolling]
Hi. Uh, it's me again.
喂，是我
Where are you? I'm sitting on the bench just outside.
你在哪？我坐在外面的长椅上
Annie ?
安妮？
Yes?
怎么了？
It's me. Charlie.
是我，查理
Hey, you.
你好呀
God, I can't believe it's really you.
天哪，我不敢相信这是你
Look at you. You're gorgeous.
哇，你真美
Is this a joke?
这是在搞笑么？
What?
什么？
No, it's me, Charlie.
没有，我是查理
What's wrong?
怎么了？
You're not 25.
你不是25岁
Oh. Well, hey.
呃 恩
Don't get upset.
不要生我的气了
Annie, please.
安妮，求你了
Just give me a chance to explain.
给我个解释的机会
It's me, Charlie.
我是查理
I'm sorry, I, but--
我，我是真的抱歉，但--
Okay, all right. You're right.
好吧，算了 我错了
I just couldn't think of a way to tell you.
我真的不知道该怎么告诉你
You have to believe me.
但你得相信我
Annie, please. Please?
安妮，拜托了
Don't get upset.You're killing me here.
不要再生气了，这比杀了我还难受
Annie? It's still me. Okay?
安妮？我还是我，相信我好么？
Forget the age thing. All that stuff that we talked about?
不要纠结年龄的问题了 想想我们谈天说地的日子？
All the things that we shared? It's me. Charlie.
想想我们敞开心扉的分享彼此的故事？是我啊，查理
I'm sitting right here next to you.
我现在就坐在你身边
Why do you keep lying to me?
你为何总是撒谎？
Because of this.
因为这个
I was, I was afraid
我，我确实不知所措
that you wouldn't be mature enough to understand.
你太小，还不会明白的
Annie, when you connect with someone the way that we connected
安妮，当你遇到一个和你很默契的人
when you find a soul mate the way that we found each other
就像找到你灵魂的另一半
then nothing else matters.
你会觉得，其他一切都不重要了
I thought you were old enough to understand that.
我以为你是成熟的，是懂我的
I mean, you made me think you could handle this, Annie.
我的意思是，你让我误以为你可以接受一切了
I mean, this is ridiculous.
这一切都太荒谬了
I mean, it's me, Charlie.
我是说，我还是我，那个查理
The same guy that you've been talking to every day and every night
2个月来 日日夜夜
for the last two months.
跟你聊天的查理
I love you.
我爱你
Annie.
安妮
And I don't get why age has to change that.
我不明白为什么年龄会影响我们的感情
Can we just walk a bit? Huh?
我们出去走走，可以么？
Talk a little bit more.
再多聊会儿
Just for a couple of minutes
在我去机场前
before I have my long drive back to the airport?
聊几分钟就好
Come on. Just--
拜托，就--
I was just looking forward to seeing you so much.
我是那么的想见到你
I thought we were friends at least, Annie.
我以为我们至少是朋友啊，安妮
This remind you of anything?
没有半点的回忆？
I was just thinking that.Your year abroad in London.
我刚还在回忆 你在伦敦的那一年
All these American students come in.I saw this girl.
那么多美国学生来到我们学校 我一眼就看中了一个美眉
Love at first sight.
可谓是一见钟情
Didn't work out.I ended up with you.
可惜与她有缘无分 结果被你给收了
There.
那么
Sorry.
抱歉
(Lynn)Go ahead, spin it.
来吧，转一下
(Annie) The candy's weird. It's better without it.
加糖后很奇怪 最好不要
(Charlie) Can I have some of yours?
我可以尝下你的么？
Oh.
哦
Yeah. You win. Pistachio rocks.
哈，你赢了 开心果最赞
So Peter took off, huh?
那么彼得去大学了，是吧？
You must be so excited.
你一定很激动吧
Yeah, I'm happy for him.
是啊，真替他高兴
I'm just gonna miss him, that's all.
我就是会有些想他 没别的
I just hope he doesn't get caught up
我就是希望他不会
into that whole fraternity rush thing.
在大学里花天酒地打架斗殴
Sounds so stupid.
听起来真可笑
Yeah, there's definitely some stupid stuff involved, but
确实，有些犯傻 但
I have to say I was a Delt
我不得不告诉你 我是一个德尔特社员来的
and there were some great things about it, too.
社团也有很多不错的地方
I met some, some quality guys that I hope will be friends for life.
最近我就结交了一些不错的朋友，能成为人生的挚友
Yeah, I just, when he drinks he kind of loses control.
我得解释下，他喝多了就发疯
This one time he tried to text me the sound of him vomiting.
有一次，他非要把他类似呕吐的声音发短信给我
It's kind of tough to spell.
描述有些困难 我懂
it's kind of-- I, I don't know.
有点那什么---我也说不清
It's like, "UG," I don't know. But...
应该是类似“哦耶~~”这样的声音 我也不太确定，但是...
I just hope he doesn't just do it to party and get laid.
我希望他不要在派对上发生那种糗事
But, yeah, I guess that's what college is for, right?
但话又说回来，大学就这回事儿吧
Finding out for yourself,finding out who you are.
寻找自己，看清自我
What?
什么？
Nothing.
没事
It's just
你还真
you amaze me. Seriously.
你已经让我着迷了 真的
You're so intelligent and sensitive, like
你聪明，敏感
wise beyond your years.
你的聪慧超越了你的年龄
It's just amazing,that's all.
这太神奇了
Hey.
嗨
Want me to teach you the secret Delt handshake?
你们想让我展示德尔特绝门握手招数么？
Okay.
来啊
You can't tell anyone.
这可是绝密
I won't.
不会说的
Okay.
好
Stick out your hand
伸出你的手
like you're gonna shake mine.
做出要跟我握手的姿势
So--
然后---
So.
这样
You still mad at me?
你还在生我气？
No, not really.
没有
Wanna check outyour present?
想看看你的礼物么？
Oh, yeah.
好啊
You said you'd want one in red, so--
你说想要一个红色的，所以--
It's sexy, right?
很性感吧？
I can't tell you how many times I've thought about you in it.
我无数次在梦中见你穿这个
It's crazy, I'm so nervous and excited
我知道这很疯狂 终于能见到你，坐在你身边
to be sitting here with you finally a ter all this time.
我很紧张，也很兴奋
There.
好了
Happy?
如愿了？
You lookridiculously sexy.
你太性感了
No, don't go.
不要走
I'm serious.
我是认真的
Come here.
过来
Come sit down.
坐下
(Charlie) Have you thought about us like this?
你有想过我们这么亲近么？
I know you have because you told me about it, didn't you?
我知道你有，你告诉过我，记得么？
(Annie) You don't think my body's weird?
你不觉得我的身体奇怪？
Are you kidding?
开什么玩笑
You're,you're gorgeous.
你，你美的让我窒息
So you're not-- disappointed or anything?
你没有觉得失望？
Annie. Annie.
安妮，安妮
You're perfect.
你是如此完美，真的
You takemy breath away.
你简直让我神魂颠倒
Can I just--?
我能不能--
No, wait, Charlie, wait.Hold on.
不要，查理，等一下
It's okay.
没关系的
Charlie--
查理---
It's okay.
不要怕
Charlie, wait.
查理，等等
Charlie.
查理
It's okay, Annie. Don't worry.
没关系安妮不要怕
I'm justtaking these off
我先把这这些脱了
Oh. Hold still, Annie. I've gotta take these off too.
别动安妮，这个也要脱
That's my girl.
我的宝贝
Oh, God.Look at you.
喔 神啊 真是个尤物
[kissing and gentle sobbing]
[接吻和各种喘息声]
(Charlie)This is perfect.
多么完美
(Lynn) How about the boys in class?
班里的男同学怎么样？
(Kate)They 're okay.
都挺好的
(Lynn) Are they?
都挺好？
(Kate) Um, we're making bowls in pottery class, but
我们在陶器课上要做陶瓷碗，但是
mine looks like an ashtray
我做出来的像个烟灰缸
which is kind of funny，because I don't smoke.
搞笑的是我从来都不吸烟
(Lynn) Nice.
很好
How 'bout you, Annie? How's school?
安妮，你呢？在学校习惯么？
Annie.
安妮
Hm ?
啊？
School.How is it?
学校 怎么样啊？
(Lynn)Annie ?
安妮？
(girl)He's so cute.
他好可爱
(Serena)I know.
我知道
You should go out with him.
你应该去约他
(Brit)Did you get my text?
收到我的短信了没？
Mm-hm.
嗯
Why didn't you call me back?
那怎么不给我回电话？
(girl 2) Check it out, Annie.Your boyfriend.
快看啊，安妮 你男朋友
(girls)OW!
哇
I told you before.He's not my boyfriend.
我告诉过你 他不是我男朋友
(girl 2) You keep saying that.Makes me think you like him.
你老是掩饰 肯定是喜欢他
If you're so obsessed with him, why you fuck him?
既然你对他这么着迷 干脆去上了他啊
- What's your problem? - Yeah? He's cute!
- 你火什么火？- 怎么了？你不是说他很可爱么！
(Annie)Pick up, please pick up.
接啊，快接啊
(Brit)ls this about Charlie?
这全是因为查理么？
(Annie)No. No.
不是
(Brit)Annie, what happened?
安妮，你怎么了？
That was him at the mall, wasn't it?
商场里看到的就是他，对不对？
How old is he?
他多大？
It doesn't matter.
这不重要
Annie, wait.
安妮，等等
Oh, my God.
天哪
(Annie) It 's not that big a deal.
没什么大不了的
We me! up on Saturday. We had sex.
我们周六见面了 我们上床了
(Annie) We're in love.
我们是相爱的
(Brit)Oh, my God.
不是吧 你犯傻了吧
Now just drop it. I'm serious.
不要再说了 我们俩是认真的
(teacher) The word ciao
“再见”一词
comes from schiavo, or servant, and was used as--
出自夏沃，以前被用来--
(woman)Sorry to interrupt, uh
不好意思打断一下，
mind if I borrow Annie Cameron for a second?
可不可以请安妮 卡梅隆出来一下
(Annie) Ms.Worley, why are we going this way?
沃利老师，找我有什么事？
Oh, it's all right,Annie. Come on in.
哦，没事，安妮 进来吧
Why don't you have a seat?
怎么不坐？
I know, yeah.
好的
Holy shit! Dude, dude.
我擦！哥们，哥们
(Will) No, it's Antigua. Anguilla is a totally different island.
不对，这是安提瓜岛 安圭拉完全是另外一码事
Honestly, I was hoping to get the crew
坦白说，鱼和熊掌
and the equipment in the same place.
我想兼得
Yeah. Hang on. Hang on just a second.
等等
Hello. Speaking.
请讲
Sorry, I,I don't understand.
不好意思 我不懂你在说什么
(Lynn)Will. Will!
威尔，威尔
What happened?
发生什么事了？
They won't tell me anything. I just, I just! got here, and I--
他们什么都不肯告诉我 我就，我就刚到，然后--
Excuse me. Annie Cameron. We're the parents.
打扰一下，安妮 卡梅隆 我们是她的家长
Let me find the nurse.
我来找护士
Mr. and Mrs. Cameron?
卡梅隆夫妇？
I'm Officer Gomez.
我是戈麦斯警长
Your daughter wants you to know that she's okay, but
你们的女儿托我告诉你们 她没什么事
maybe you should have a seat.
来坐吧
- What's going on? - What?
- 这到底是怎么了？- 怎么了？
We don't know exactly what's happened.
我们也不太清楚到底发生了什么
What we do know so far
目前我们知道的是
is that we think she was assaulted
她3天前遭受她所谓的
by her alleged boyfriend three days ago.
男朋友的殴打
She hasn't got a boyfriend.
她没有什么男朋友
Well, apparently on Saturday
呃，貌似上周六开始她有了
she met up with a man she calls Charlie
她去旅馆见了这个叫查理的男子
at a motel, where she was sexually assaulted.
在那里她遭到了性虐待
The man is at least 35 years old.
这个男子至少有35岁
Jesus Christ.Where is she?
老天啊 她现在在哪？
She's in an exam room with the nurse
护士带她在监护室
collecting evidence for the rape kit.She's okay.
采集遭受强奸的证据 她没事
One of the counselors from the hospital is with her.
医院的一个顾问在陪护她
I have to see her.
我要见她
Look, there is a private waiting room just down the hall--
听着，客厅处有一个私人等候室
We have to see her right now!
我们要立马见她！
We want to see her right now.
我们现在就要见她
She's having an exam. You'll see her in a minute.
她正在做检查 很快就出来
(nurse)I'm almost done.
很快就好
I just need to get one more picture of that abrasion.
再拍一张宫颈损伤的图片
(Will) This is fucking insane.
这他妈是疯了
On, baby.
宝贝儿
It's okay. We're here.We're here now.
没事的，我们在这里 我们在你身边
Mr. and Mrs. Cameron, I'm Gail Friedman.
卡梅隆夫妇 我是盖尔 弗里德曼
I'm a counselor with the hospital.
我是这家医院的顾问
I'm glad you're here.
你来了就好
- Annie here is an amazing young woman. - Gail.
- 安妮是一个很坚强的女孩  - 盖尔
- Ah. This is Special Agent Doug Tate with the FBI. - Hi.
- 对了，这是FBI的特工道格.塔特
FBI? FBI
(Doug) Well, any time a crime is committed
是的，一切涉及未成年网络犯罪
against a child using the Internet
或者犯罪嫌疑人非美国公民的案子
and the suspect is a traveler
并且嫌犯在逃的话
someone from out of state, they call us in.
我们都要负责调查
Look, Annie, I know you've had a rough day.
听着，安妮 我知道今天对你来说很难熬
But I need to ask you a couple of questions.You feel up for it?
但现在我需要问你几个问题 你可以协助我们么？
Do we have to do this now?
非要现在问么？
Trust me, the sooner we start this investigation, the better.
相信我，越早开始调查越快抓住罪犯
Gail, do we still have the clothes she was wearing that night?
盖尔，那晚她穿的衣服是否还在？
- Yes.- Are they here?
- 是的 - 现在在你手上么？
No, they're at her house.
不在，衣服在她家里
Okay, I need to get those from you as soon as possible.
好，你尽快拿给我
Is that okay?
有问题么？
Yeah, I guess.
没有
Mr. Cameron,Mrs.
卡梅隆夫妇
I would like to talk to Annie alone.Could you please just--
我需要单独跟安妮谈一会 你们可不可以--
Look, I've had enough of this.
听着，我受够 这一切了
This is our daughter. We wanna be with her.
她是我们的女儿 我们要陪在她身边
(Gail) You've got to understand that right now
你们现在必须清楚
Annie's a victim of a crime and you and your wife are just witnesses.
安妮是一宗案件的受害者 你跟你太太只是证人
That's why we interview everybody separately
因此我们必须与每个人单独谈话
so as not to contaminate anyone's testimony.
以确保证人的口供真实性
Now if you can just give Annie and I a second alone
现在请给我和小安妮一点时间
and then I'll come back to your house
我还会去你们家
and we can all sit down and talk.
与你们谈话
Fair enough?
可以么？
(Lynn) So how long will this take ?
要多久才能抓到他？
Well, it depends if we get enough genetic material to run a profile.
那要看我们是否能收集到一些有利证据
And if there is, how long?
如果能收集到，要多久？
Right now, there's a nationwide backlog.
现在全国的案子非常多
In Illinois alone, we've got 2,000 unopened kits
仅在伊利诺伊州，我们还有2000起
sitting in freezers waiting to be processed.
棘手案件等待处理
Some people have been waiting a year.
有些人等了一年
- What? - How is that possible?
- 什么 - 怎么可能？
We'll run this through the FBI facilities.
我们通过FBI运作
So, two weeks, a month on the outside.
所以 2周，或者1个月
A month?
一个月？
Now can I see the family computer?
我能不能看下你们家的电脑？
(man)Doug.
道格
Yeah.
是
- Did you copy the hard drive? - Yup.
- 硬盘拷贝了么？- 拷贝好了
- We'll take that with the evidence down to the lab. - Okay.
- 把这些证据都拿到实验室 - 好的
Apart from Teen Chat
除了少年聊天网，
were there any other networking sites
还有没有别的社交网络站点？
you used to communicate?
你还有没有使用其他网络聊天工具？
No, not really.
没有
Did you guys ever speak on the phone?
你们俩有没有通过电话？
You spoke to him.
你跟他还通过电话
(Doug) Now, you said his mother was sick.
你说他的妈妈得病了
Yeah. Cancer.
是的 癌症
Yeah, okay.
那么好
Tell him you feel awful about his mother
告诉他你对他妈妈的病感到惋惜
that you really wanna talk to him
非常想听听他的声音
that you lost an uncle to cancer.
说你曾经有个叔叔也得了癌症
I-I don't know.
我-我不确定
You don't know what?
不确定什么？
I just don't wanna lie to him.
我就是不想对他撒谎
What are you talking about, sweetheart? He lied to you.
你在说什么啊，孩子？他对你撒谎了
(Lynn) What do you think of writing to him
你觉得要不要给他写封信
and just telling him how you feel?
告诉他你的感受？
(Doug) Yeah, Annie. Would that be good?
对，安妮 那样会不会更好？
Yeah, I guess.
可能是吧
Okay, good.
那好
(Doug) Okay, just keep if simple- Be yourself
写简单一些，用你的口气写
Maybe he didn't even like me.
或许他根本就不喜欢我
He didn't.
确实不喜欢
(Lynn) Will!
威尔！
(Will) it wasn't like that, sweetheart.
不是你想的那样，宝贝儿
The man tricked you.
这个男人骗了你
(Will)What?
什么？
- (Will) Is that him?- Charlie.
- 是他么？- 查理
(Doug) Okay, now, remember, he's gonna test you
现在好了，他肯定先要探你的口风
to see if you told anybody.You haven't, okay?
看你有没有告诉别人发生的事情 假装你什么都没说过，知道么？
Tell him that you're concerned
告诉他你很担心
and a little worried thathe hasn't called. Okay?
想知道他为何不给你打电话
Should I?
我要这么说么？
Yeah, answer him. Yeah.
是的，快接电话
(Will) A-are, are you guys tracing this?
你们在跟踪这家伙么？
Yes.
是的
It says private. What do I do to answer it?
是私人号码 我要接么？
(Doug)Frank, are we good?
弗兰克 ，准备好了没？
We're good.
好了
(Doug) Annie? Look at me? Just, just talk to him.
安妮？看着我，跟他谈话，聊天
All right?
可以么？
Okay.
嗯
Hello?
喂？
(Charlie)Annie ?
安妮？
Charlie?
查理？
Hi.
嗨
(Charlie) It's kinda late. Where are your parents?
现在很晚了 你父母呢？
They took Katie to the movies.
他们带卡蒂去看电影了
Charlie?
查理？
Shit.
糟了
(Charlie) Shame on you, Annie. [hangs up]
安妮你耍我
Charlie?
查理?
Charlie, are you there?
查理,在听么？
Charlie?
查理？
Damn it!
该死！
Frank, did we get it?
弗兰克 ，追踪到了么？
Well, that's it. He's gone.
时间太短 让他跑了
Why did you make me do that?
为什么你们要我这么做？
Annie!
安妮！
(Doug) He probably got your cell number off your website.
他很可能是从你的主页上弄到你的号码的
(Doug) Look, I'll give you a call
我从旅馆回来后
when I get back from the motel.
会给你打个电话
Tell me something. Did she yell for help?
告诉我 她有没有呼叫救命？
I mean, did she scream, tell him to stop?
我的意思是，她有没有尖叫 让他停手？
Just because she didn't scream for help
只是因为她没有呼喊，并不代表
does not mean this wasn't rape.
这不是强奸
Now that guy is 20 years older than she is.
那个男人比他大20岁
He groomed her for weeks just to get her into the motel room
他计划了好几个礼拜，就是为了带她去开房
and she's armed with what? The eighth-grade biology
她的武器是什么？
and the expectation that the world is a decent place.
8年级的生物学知识，还有一个对纯洁世界的单纯期望？
I'm gonna fucking kill this guy.
我他妈要杀了他
No, you won't. That's why I'm here. Now, we will find him.
你不能冲动 我们在这里，我们会找到他的
And what am I supposed to do?
那我该怎么做？
You go back inside, you support your daughter
你进屋去，你要做的是支持你的女儿
and you let us do our job.
其他的交给我们
What, with just five of you guys working the whole state?
整个美国只有你们5个警察在工作么？
There's gotta be something I can do. I'm not just gonna stand around and wait--
我肯定能帮上忙我不能坐观其变，只是在这里傻等---
Mr. Cameron, I promise you.
卡梅隆先生，我向你保证
I put everything I got into these cases.
我会尽自己最大努力侦破这个案子
You just gotta give us a chance.
给我们时间
Now, my cell is on the back.
我的号码在背面
You call me if you need anything.
有任何情况给我打电话
I'll drop you a line tomorrow when I get back from the motel.
明天从旅馆回来我会给你信息
(Lynn) You want me to sleep with you tonight?
我今晚陪你睡好么？
No, I just want my blanket.
不用了 把我的被子给我
[Annie, sobbing] No, please, stop.
不要 不要啊
(Annie) Stop, please!
求你停下来
Dad, please help me to stop him.
爸爸，让他停止
Please, Dad, help!
爸爸，救我啊
[screaming] Help me! No, get off!
救我！不要，走开！
Don't Please, Dad, help me, please.
不要，求你了！爸爸，求你救救我！
Stop! No!
不要！
(Al)Will.
威尔
You all right, buddy?
你还好吧？
Yeah, of course.
没事
If Mrs. Van Dersey wants the meeting, fine.
要是范.德西女士想开会，让她开吧
But I think that we should dictate the parameters.
但是我们得规定好参数
No more of this bullshit.
别给我扯其他的屁话
Good.
很好
Is there any more coffee?
还有咖啡么？
Grab another coffee.
再来一杯
(Will) Hey. I got you a new cell.
嗨 我给你买了新手机
Now, you have to promise me
答应我，
that you're not gonna try and call him
不要再给他打电话
or text him with this new number.
或者发短信了
Remember what Tate said about the old one
还记得塔特怎么说这家伙的么
that if he tries to call you on that, you tell us immediately.
如果他给你打电话，立刻告诉我们
I'm gonna have to check the bills.
我会去查电话账单
And if I find out that you've tried to contact him
如果我发现你联系过他
I'm gonna have to take it back.
我就把这个电话没收
Okay?
明白么？
So what? Do I just start talking like Tony Soprano?
我是不是开始像托尼.瑟普拉诺一样说话了？（注：托尼是一美剧男猪脚，从小受过刺激，有忧郁症）
Boy, I hope not.
千万不要
I'm glad you came.
很高兴你能来
Yeah, well, my parents said I had to.
我爸妈说我必须来
Well, even so,I'm still glad.
尽管如此，我仍然很欣慰
I want this to be a place
我希望在这里
for you to feel safe and comfortable
可以让你忘记那些不愉快
talking about anything.
在这里畅所欲言
I just wanna be helpful to you.
我希望能竭尽所能帮助你
You think I need help?
你觉得我有病？
I think that what you've been through must be very difficult.
我只是觉得你的经历很惨痛
You know, what's the big deal?
你知道么，没什么大不了的
There are girls at my school
在我们学校有很多女生
who've had sexwith half the football team.
甚至被半个足球队的男生上过
I lose my virginity and my parents
我只是失身而已，
make a federal case out of it.
我爸妈却要惊动联邦局调查这件事
Literally.
大惊小怪
I think they're more concerned
其实他们
that you may have been in danger
最最担心的
more than anything else.
是你身处危险
Danger?
危险？
That's 'cause they don't know him.
他们不了解他
You know, the thing is
知道么
I bet my dad would really like him
在这件事之前，如果我爸爸
if they'd met, you know, before.
见到查理，我打赌他会喜欢他
What is it about him you think your father would like ?
你觉得你爸爸会喜欢他哪一点呢？
He's sweet, and smart, and really funny.
他可爱，聪明，并且非常幽默
And gives great advice and which, by the way, worked.
他给我很多 行得通的建议
I-I made the team because of him.
我能加入团队也是因为他
You think that's the only reason you made the team?
你以为是他帮你入团的？
Because of his advice, and not your own ability?
是因为他的建议，而不是你的能力？
Well, he's older. He's been playing longer.
他比我大 比我的技术好
What'd you think about him being older?
他年龄这么大，你不介意么？
At first I thought he was 16, okay?
一开始我以为他16岁
And then, all of a sudden he's 20 and I'm like, what?
突然得知他20岁了，我就纠结了
And then we kept talking
但后来我们继续交流
and I was, like, what's the big deal?
我觉得没什么大不了的
He gets me, you know?
他吸引了我，你明白么？
He's not judgmental.
他不会对我评头论足
He's encouraging.
他总是鼓励我
And despite my age difference he still loves me.
尽管年龄上有差距，他还是爱我的
And he thinks I'm beautiful.
他觉得我很美
What'd you think about him
对他隐瞒自己的真实年龄
not being honest about his age?
你是怎么看的？
You know, Charlie said that
查理告诉我
when you connect like we did
当你找到与你默契的人
when you find that soul mate
当你发现你灵魂的另一半
that's the only thing to think about.
你会觉得，其他一切都是浮云
Don't you believe that when two people are in love
你不这么认为么？俩个人坠入爱河
nothing else matters?
其他一切都是浮云？
I can understand how strong those feelings are, Annie.
我完全能体会你对他的感情，安妮
But, there are reasons why girls your age and men his
但是，你太小了 不该和他那个年龄的大叔走在一起
aren't supposed to be together.
有很多原因
Whatever.
随你怎么说
He loves me. I know he does.
他爱我 我知道他爱我
And he's dying to call me or email me
他非常想给我打电话， 给我发邮件
but he knows it's no! safe
但是他知道很危险
thanks to my parents and the FBI.
这都是拜我父母还有那些FBI所赐
I just--
我就是希望--
What?
希望什么
I just hope he's okay.
我希望他没事就好
What, he go to lunch early?
什么？他提前去吃午饭了？
He went home.Said he wasn't feeling well.
他回家了 说他不舒服
Hello?
喂
Will, it's Agent Tate.
威尔，我是塔特探员
I wanted to give you an update.
我有消息告诉你
Now, look, the motel didn't give us much.
旅馆里没有什么有价值的线索
He paid cash for the room.
他付的是现金
He told the manager he lost his wallet.
他告诉旅馆老板他钱包丢了
He even ordered a credit card right in front of him.
他甚至在他面前办理挂失
The, uh, the cell phone was prepaid. It was purchased in St. Louis.
电话是在圣路易斯买的预缴费号码
He paid cash for that, too, whoever he is.
也是现金买的，没有用名字
So his name's not Charles Hightower.
所以，他的名字 很可能不叫查理海陶尔
Yeah, not that we can tell.
目前来看不是
I found seven of them living in the U.S. so far
我在美国找到7个叫这个名字的
but none of 'em fit the description.
没有一个符合他的特征
There 's nothing that even confirms he's from California
也没有确凿证据证明他来自加利福利亚
we, uh, we actually traced his IP address to the Czech Republic.
实际上我们跟踪他的地址 地址显示是在捷克
What?
什么？
It seems he's running some sort of ghost program.
他使用了电脑特洛伊程序
It's a software that basically bounces
基本上
his IP address from one server to another
这个程序可以使
all over the world.
他的IP地址在全世界范围内自由变换
Sir?
先生？
Sorry, I don't understand.
抱歉 我完全听不懂
What does that mean?
什么意思？
It means he's good at what he's doing.
意思就是，他是有组织有预谋的犯罪高手
But don't worry, don't worry. This is exactly how it starts.
不要担心，这是刚开始
You need to go on through, go get your stuff.
你需要继续合作 去拿你的东西吧
Yeah, one minute, please.
给我一分钟
What about the car? Anything?
那部车呢？有什么发现？
Hang up the phone, sir.
挂掉电话
It was an airport rental. He must've swapped the plates.
那部车是机场租来的， 他肯定是换了牌照
Gary!
加里！
(Will) Look, I'm, I'll have to call you back. Okay?
听着，我会给你电话的
Seriously, is my conversation
拜托，难道我的私人通话
that much of a threat to security?
也会威胁到机场安全吗？
Thank you, sir.
谢谢 先生
Is it over?
结束了？
Yeah, you missed a pretty good fight.
是啊 你错过了一场好戏
(Lynn) When they do Real Housewives of Chicago
如果他们要在芝加哥拍真正的主妇，
I am so auditioning.
我一定要去视镜
Yeah, right.
嗯 是啊
I talked to Jennie.
我跟珍妮谈了一下
Brittany's really upset you won't call her back.
你没有给布兰特妮回电话，她非常伤心
Good.
很好
She was only trying to help, honey.
她只是想帮忙，亲爱的
Yeah, well, she's a bitch.
是么 她只是个骚货
No, she's your best friend.
她是你最好的朋友
Best friends don't narc on each other.
好朋友不会背叛彼此
Not like she'll ever get a boyfriend
不会期望自己的朋友没有男朋友
but if she does, I hope someone ruins it for her, too.
更不会破坏朋友的感情
(Will)Lynn ?
琳恩？
(Will) Did you get my message?
收到我的信息了么？
Yeah, I called you back
有收到，我给你回电话了
but it went to voice mail. Did you eat?
但是直接进入了语音留言 你吃饭了么？
Have a look at this a second.
过来看看这个
You won't believe this.
你肯定不敢相信
What is this?
什么东西？
This is the National Sex Offenders Registry.
这是国家性侵案件逃犯的资料库
There's perverts all over Wilmette, not just Chicago.
不只芝加哥，整个Wilmette都存在
See this? All these red dots.
看到这个没？所有这些红点区域
They're everywhere.
到处都是
Oh, my God.
哦 天哪
This guy here is literally three blocks away on Linden.
这个变态离我们林登区只有三个街道远
What's going on?
怎么了？
Hi, sweetheart. Um, come here a second.
嗨 亲爱的 过来一下
I, I need you to do something for me.
我需要你帮我做件事
These men are all registered sex offenders in the neighborhood
这些男人都是住在附近
that fit the description.
符合特征的性侵犯嫌疑人
I need you to look through them.
你要认真看看
Why?
干嘛？
In case one of them's Charlie.
其中一个可能就是查理
What?
什么？
No. N-- No.
不 不
(Lynn) Honey, you should. One of them could be him.
亲爱的，你必须得帮忙 找出这个混蛋
None of them's him.
不会有他的
Forget the hair and the mustaches. Just look at the face.
忽略发型与胡子 只观察脸部特征就好
Could any of them be him?
你说这些人中会不会有个就是他？
I said, no.
不会的
God, what's your problem?
爸，你还正常么？
My problem is you were attacked.
我是不正常，因为你被人伤害了
It wasn't like that.
根本不是那样的
Besides, none of them are Charlie, okay?
再说了，查理真的不在这里面
Are we done?
可以了么？
(Lynn) Pervert Tracker. What is this?
变态跟踪者 这是什么？
It's a group I met with today.
是今天我遇到的一个团伙
(Will) Supposed to be the best in the country. They hunt predators.
听说是全国最强的 他们到处追踪罪犯
Today? It says they're in New Jersey.
今天？ 这里说他们在新泽西州
You were in New Jersey today?
你今天在新泽西？
You got on a plane today without telling me?
你没告诉我就坐飞机去了新西泽？
Are you fucking kidding me ?
你丫的开什么玩笑？
I swear to God, Will
我告诉你，威尔，
if you ever get on a plane again without telling me
下次你再没经过我同意就坐飞机
I swear to God, I don't know what I'd do.
我就让你好看
I'm sorry.
对不起
Honey, you're right. I'm sorry.
亲爱的  对不起
I'm gonna go check on her.
我去看看她
(Annie) I've gotta get out of my house.
我必须得离开这里
How come? What's happening at home?
怎么了？ 家里发生什么事了？
You know, they think I'm stupid for meeting up with him.
知道么，他们都觉得我与他见面
Going back to his hotel.
与他去开房很愚蠢
They said that?
他们这么说的？
My dad looks at me like I'm an idiot.
我爸现在就把我当个傻B
He wants to kill Charlie.That's all he talks about.
他甚至想杀了查理
Getting his hands on him.
他想揍扁他
Well, what would you do if he got in touch with you
那如果他又联系到你怎么办？
have you thought about what you would say to him?
你想好跟他说什么了么？
I just wanna talk to him.Hear his voice.
我只是想跟他说说话 听听他的声音
See how his mom's doing, and his little dog.
看看他妈妈在忙什么 还有他的狗狗的近况
See how we're gonna make this work.
看看我们能不能渡过这个难关
I just wanna talk to him about what happened.
我就想跟他谈谈 发生的这一切
We haven 'I really talked about that
旅馆里发生的一切
about what happened in the motel.
我们俩都没有谈过
Are we supposed to?
我们该谈么？
In my experience, it helps. It really does.
在我看来 我们应该谈谈 这对你有帮助
But only if you're ready.
但前提是你已经做好了准备
Li's kind of weird, you know.
这感觉有点怪怪的
Like it wasn't really happening to me.
好像这一切都不是真的发生在我身上
Like I was watching it from above.
我就像是个旁观者
Sometimes when you can't physically escape from a situation
有时候，当你身陷危险却无法逃脱
where you feel frightened or threatened
当你受到威胁恐吓的时候
you find a way to remove or distance yourself psychologically.
你的心理上会寻找解脱
It's a way of protecting yourself.
这是自我保护的方法
Does that make sense?
这个解释合理吧？
Still have ten minutes.
还有10分钟
Yeah, well. I'll see you later.
嗯，回聊
(Al) Chicago has a very strong sense of history.
芝加哥有相当久远的历史
Kinda like when they bought Marshall Fields, turned it into a Macy's.
他们买下了马歇尔地，把它变成了梅西百货
They lost half their client base.
他们失去了一半的客户群
(Will) It's a fine line. You want a fresh look
这也很正常 你想要尝试新的领域
but you don't want to alienate your loyal customers.
但你又不想疏远老客户
We loved what you did with A & A
我们很佩服你和A&A
particularly in the tween market.
空挡市场的处理手段
Well, that was mostly Will's work here.
呵呵 那基本是威尔的功劳
Well, I don't know if that's true
呃 不管这话是真是假
but I'm very happy to take the credit.
我表示愿意接受奖赏
(man)Rebecca?
丽贝卡？
Becky.
贝姬
Jerry?
杰里?
Yeah.
对
Hi, Jerry.
嗨 杰里
Look at you. You're gorgeous.
看看你，你真美
(Becky over mic) You really think so ?
你真这么认为？
(Jerry over mic) Yeah. Can't believe it's you.
是啊，我不敢相信这是你
Did you bring your stuff?
你带来你的东西了么？
(Jerry) Uh--
噢--
Fuck!
我操
(Doug) Hey! Hey! Stop! FBI!
喂 喂 等等 FBI
(Becky) Hey, get that guy!
喂 抓住那个家伙！
(Doug) Go, guys, get him, get him! Come on!
上去抓住那个家伙 快！
Hey!
嘿
Actually, there's a lot of similarities
事实上，你的公司与学校
between your company and Academic Appeal.
有许多相似的地方
It's just you have a much more sophisticated client base.
只是你的客户更加复杂
Everybody wants to broaden their consumer appeal
每个人都想增强对客户的吸引力
especially in the tween market.
特别是在青少年市场
I mean, it's like the Holy Grail of--
意思是说，这就像圣杯的--
Sorry, would you just excuse me a minute?
不好意思，走开一下
(Doug) Look, I'm really sorry, Will.
听着威尔，我非常抱歉
So what made you think he was our guy?
你为什么觉得他就是我们要找的人？
The program he was running to scatter his IP address
他运行的那个程序可以伪造IP地址
the chat rooms he used.
他在聊天室里使用过
Mostly, Will, it was his conversation.
可以这么说，威尔,这是他的对话内容
It was the way he spoke.
他的聊天方式
It was very similar to the way Charlie chatted.
与查理的聊天方式非常相似
How do you know that?
你如何知道这个？
I was able to get transcripts of two months worth of IM chats
我调出了近两个月你女儿与他的IM聊天信息
between him and your daughter from Teen Chat.
在少年聊天室里的聊天记录
You're kidding.
你在开玩笑吧
No. I'm not.
是真的
So when can I see them?
我什么时候能看那个聊天记录？
You can't, Will.
威尔，你不能看
It's an ongoing investigation.
这个调查还在进行中
I'd completely lose Annie's trust.
我不能失去安妮的信任
Now, I do have some good news.
有个好消息要告诉你
The lab was able to extract enough DNA for a profile.
实验室可以提取足够的DNA建立档案
We're gonna run it through CODIS, the national database
我们会使用国家资料库里的数据系统
and if there's a hit we should know
就是说一但有匹配的嫌疑人
within a week or two at the most.
最多两周，我们就会跟踪到结果
Hey, I'll be right back. I gotta call in.
等等  我接个电话
(Will) Lynn.
琳恩
Will, what are you doing here?
威尔，你来这里做什么？
I just came from seeing Tate.
我刚刚见了塔特
What's wrong?
怎么回事？
You're not gonna believe this.
不可思议
What? What is this?
什么不可思议？
Read it.
看看这个
What is it?
这是什么？
Just read it.
看看就知道了
"l can't stop thinking about it."
“我忍不住去幻想”
"You inside me. I get wet when I picture it."
“你进入我身体，仅是想起就湿了”
Okay, stop.
好了 别读了
Our daughter wrote this.
这是我们的女儿写的
Annie.
安妮
"How big are you? I bet you taste good."
“你那个多大 我猜口感不错”
Will, stop it.
威尔，求你别读了
"l wanna see it right now."
“我想现在见到它”
Stop it, Jesus God!
天哪 别读了！
I mean, she's 14. Where the hell did she learn this?
我不懂 她才14岁 她从哪学到这么多的？
She's 14, she didn't make this happen!
她才14岁，这一切不是她的所作所为！
Yeah, but we're gonna have to talk to her about this.
我知道，可是我们必须 找她谈谈
- You are not gonna talk to her. - But look at it!
- 你不能去找她谈     - 你听听这些
Our daughter sounds like a fucking porn star!
我们的女儿听起来 就他妈像个AV女优
You cannot confront her about this.
你不能在她面前提这些
- I'm gonna kill him. - No.
- 我要去杀了他   - 冷静点
I swear to God, I'm gonna find
我发誓 我要找到他
this animal and I'm gonna fucking kill him!
这杂种，我他妈要把他碎尸万段
Stop it!
你疯了！
Oh, my God.You're acting crazy, Will.
天哪 威尔，你真的疯了
No, you're not gonna-- You're not gonna read this.
不，你不能-- 再看这些聊天记录了
Just leave it alone. Give it to me.
别管这个了 把它给我
I'll see you tonight.
再见
(Doug) Now I need you to bring that back to me right now, Will.
威尔，现在把它还给我吧
I'll get it back to you tomorrow.
我明天会还给你
You do know it's a federal crime, right?
你这是犯罪，你知道么？
(Will) I just think I have a right to know
我有权了解我的女儿
who my daughter's talking to.
在跟什么人聊天
No, no, no. You are interfering with the investigation.
不不不，你已经干扰了我们的调查
You've betrayed your daughter's trust to me.
你会让你的女儿对我失去信任
She doesn't need to know.
我不会让她知道的
You're not letting me do my job, Mr. Cameron.
卡梅隆先生，你在影响我的工作
I need you to bring them back to me right now, Will.
威尔，我再说一遍，立马还给我
Yeah, I will. I'll get it back to you.
好吧 我给你 我会还给你
Right--
现--
Oh, you son of a bitch.
你个狗娘养的
Hey, stranger.
喂
This is something, huh?
这地方好带劲，哈？
Oh, yeah, it's great. I feel 80.
确实带劲 我觉得我80岁了
Mojito?
要杯Mojito？
I'm fine, thanks.
不用了 谢谢
(man) Hey, great party, man.
嗨 很赞的派对
(Al) Will, come here!
威尔，过来一下！
Will. Are you all right?
威尔，你还好么？
No, I'm, I'm, I'm just feeling, I'm--
不好，我觉得我--
S-- Sorry.
对--不起
Will? Will!
威尔？Will！
I heard the door.
我听到开门声
(Will) That was me.
是我
I, I couldn't sleep. I took a drive.
我，我睡不着 出去兜风了
Well, you scared me.
哦，你吓死我了
Will, you scared me.
威尔,你吓到我了
Sorry.
对不起
All right, so, are you coming up?
好吧，你不上来睡吗？
In a bit.
马上
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
Nothing.
没干嘛
Is this you?
这个是你吗？
Are you, are you Sad Little Girl?
你是，你是这个悲伤的小妞吗？
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
You're posing as a teenage girl
你冒充成十几岁的少女
to chat with men on line, seriously?
上网和男人聊天，是这样吗？
That's what they do. They showed me.
那是他们喜欢的 我不过是学他们
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天
It's a way of drawing them out.
这样就能把他们给引出来
Good night.
晚安
(Lynn) I spoke to Pete today.
我今天和彼得通电话了
He's coming home for Halloween.
他要回来过万圣节
(Lynn) Well, he said he would try. He's got a lot of work.
他说他会尽量，他有作业要做
But, and he sounds good. Happy.
不过，他听起来挺不错，很高兴
You didn't tell him, did you?
你没告诉他吧，有吗？
(Lynn) No. But I--
没有 但我--
Don't, okay?
别说，好吗？
Oh, about what? What?
噢，别说什么？什么啊？
Remember what we talked about upstairs, sweetie
记得我们在楼上说过的，亲爱的
about Annie being hurt?
安妮受伤的事？
I'm serious, okay?
我是认真的，好吗？
Okay.
好
How 'bout we go to the movies this weekend?
周末我们去看场电影怎样？
Is there anything you wanna see?
你有想看的吗？
Nothing you'd be interested in.
但我想看的 你不会喜欢的
Well, try me.I may surprise you.
呃，说来听听 可能会让你惊喜
Yeah, right.
哦，那好吧
What does that mean?
这是什么意思？
Why are you being so mean to me? What did I do?
你为什么对我不耐烦？我做了什么？
I'm not being mean.
我没有不耐烦
Katie, am I being mean?
卡蒂,我有吗？
(Kate)No.
没有
How 'bout we go on a bike ride this weekend?
这周末我们骑车出去怎样？
(Kale) Well, yeah. Uh, can we also go along the lake?
好啊 呃，能沿着湖边骑吗？
Yeah. And we can go to that favorite rock that you like.
当然可以 我们还可以去你最喜欢的岩石那
Cool.
太好了
(Annie) Great.
很好
(Lynn) You know, you don'I have to do this, honey.
你知道你可以不去的，宝贝
Yeah, I know.
嗯，我知道
Well, call me if you need anything, okay?
有事给我打电话，知道吗？
Honey? Give me a kiss.
宝贝？亲一下
I love you.
我爱你
See you later.
再见
Okay.
好
You're gonna have to talk to me sometime.
你总要跟我说话吧
I'm really sorry, Annie, okay?
我很抱歉，安妮，好吗？
I didn't know what else to do.
我当时真不知道该怎么办了
Annie?
安妮？
You're sorry?
你很抱歉？
Yeah.
是的
Do you realize what you did?
你知道你做了什么吗？
You fucked up everything.
你毁了一切
Charlie, my parents, everything.
查理，我爸妈，一切！
I was scared, okay?
我当时很害怕，原谅我好吗？
No. It's not okay.
不，一点都不好
I kept every secret of yours.
你所有的秘密我都守口如瓶
Annie, you're my best friend and I was worried about you.
安妮，你是我最好的朋友，我很担心你
"Was." I was your best friend.
“曾经是”我曾经是你最好的朋友
Do me a favor and never talk to me again.
拜托你，别再和我说话了
Annie.
安妮
Annie!
安妮！
(Al) That was fucking embarrassing at the big launch party.
你在午餐派对上那样还真够丢人的
Oh, yeah, I know,I'm sorry.
是的，我知道，对不起
It was just some personal stuff. It was nothing.
只是一点私事 没什么
You're sure?
你确定吗？
Because you've been kind of MIA around here lately.
因为你最近总在这里给我玩失踪
There just could not be a worse time to be distracted
在我最需要你专心投入工作的时候
while I really need your head in the game.
你却分心，太不是时候了
What, you don't think I'm giving a 100%, Coach?
你觉得我没有尽力在做吗，领导？
Well, you tell me. I put this on your desk a week ago.
好吧，你告诉我 我一周前就把这个放在你桌上了
Mel's been waiting since Monday for you to sign off on this.
梅尔从周一就在等你在这上面签字
Well, tell him, then, fine. Run with it.
那就跟他说好了 就这么办
You haven't even looked at it, have you?
你看都没看过一眼，是吧？
What the hell's going on?
到底发生了什么事？
It's Annie.
是安妮
She was sexually assaulted.
她被人性侵犯了
What?
什么？
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天
I had no idea, Will.
不好意思 我完全不知道，威尔
She's fine.
I mean, she wasn't, but she's okay.
我是说，不是 她...但她没事
They catch the guy?
他们抓到人了吗？
They're looking for him.
他们正在找
They started with the crime scene in the motel.
他们从旅馆的作案现场开始
Jesus. She was kidnapped?
天啊 他被绑架了吗？
No, she-- She sort of knew the guy.
不，她--她可以说是认识那个人的
I-- I don't understand.
我--我不明白
It was someone she met online
是她在网上认识的一个人
someone she'd been talking to for a while.
她和他聊过一段时间
Oh, I thought you meant she was like attacked, you know. I--
噢，我以为你是说她被那样侵犯了，你知道 我--
You scared the shit out of me.
被你突然这么说我有些不知所措
She was raped.
她被强奸了
She's 14. The guy's in his 30s.
她才14，那人已经30多岁了
I know, I know. It's just that I was picturing--
我知道，我知道 我刚刚是在想--
Well, you don't wanna know what I was picturing.
呃，你不会想知道我想了什么
Could have been much worse.
也可能是更糟的
[Will, knocking] Hey, can I come in?
嘿，我能进来吗？
I guess. What's up?
可以 什么事？
How was school?
在学校怎么样？
Okay.
挺好
Was it weird seeing your friends again?
再见到朋友们会不会觉得怪怪的？
It was fine, Dad.
还好，爸爸
Did you see Gail today?
今天见到盖尔了吗？
No, tomorrow.
没有，明天
How, how's that going?
怎样，进行得怎样了？
Great. I'm cured.
很顺利 我没事了
Still no contact from "Charlie"?
还没有和“查理”联系吗？
I hate when you do that.
我讨厌你这样
Say his name like that.
这样说他的名字
It's not his real name, is it?
这不是他的真名，对吗？
What do you want, Dad?
你想知道什么，爸爸？
Has there been any contact?
还有联系吗？
No.
没有
None at all?
一点都没有？
What, you don't believe me?
怎么，你不相信我？
You wanna check my phone?
要查我的手机吗？
Would you have a problem with that?
你会介意吗？
Yeah, I would.
是，我会
Why, if there's nothing to hide
为什么，如果没什么要隐瞒的话
why would that be a problem?
为什么会介意？
You're unbelievable.
你真让人不可置信
What?
什么？
Take it. What's your problem?
拿走吧 你怎么了？
What is my problem? My problem is you lied to me, sweetheart.
我怎么了？是你对我说谎啊，孩子
From the second that you knew he wasn't 15, you should have told me
你刚知道他不是15岁的时候，就应该告诉我
and you didn't. You lied.
但你没有 你还撒谎
Why didn't you come and talk to me or your mother
你为什么不来跟我或你妈妈商量
and say what was going on?
说说发生了什么事？
When you found out for the first time, what--
当你刚刚发现时，你在--
What were you thinking?
你在想什么？
You didn't know then that something was wrong?
当时你没怀疑过他吗？
When you, you met him in the mall and saw him for the first time
当你在商场第一次见到他时
what do you do, you don't call me? You don't run away?
你在做什么，为什么不告诉我？你为什么不走掉？
You get in a car with him? it's like rule number one.
你居然跟着他上车？这是最不该做的事
You know, I'm trying to understa--
你知道吗，我很想弄明白--
Please just leave me alone.
求你别再烦我了
But talk to me. I--
跟我说说 我--
You're just pissed you didn't know.
难道你只是因为这件事而生气
No, that's not--
不，不是的--
No, everything would've been fine
不，如果每个人都能冷静一点
if everyone would've just chilled out.
就什么事都没有了
- What are you talking about? - Charlie and me.
- 你在说什么？-查理和我
Are you out of your mind?
你是不是疯了？
You're the crazy one!
你才疯了！
Checking my phone,
查我的手机，
bringing out sickos on the web.
在网上上找变态男人
I'm trying to find the scumbag!
我想找出那个王八蛋！
He's not like that!
他不是！
You don't even know him!
你根本就不认识他！
My God, you're protecting him. The guy raped you.
我的天，你在替他说话 那家伙强奸了你
And you're protecting him.
你还替他说话
He didn't rape me!
他没有强奸我！
Get out, get out of my fucking room right now!
出去，马上滚出去！
I hate you. Get out!
我讨厌你，出去！
Get out!
出去！
Get out of my room!
从我房间出去！
I just wanted to know how Annie's doing.
我只是想知道安妮的情况
You know I can't discuss her treatment with you, Mr. 卡梅隆.
你知道我不能和你讨论她的治疗问题，卡梅隆先生
I'm sorry, but this still doesn't make sense to me.
我很抱歉，但这样我还是不能理解
She's my daughter. A minor.
她是我的女儿，还未成年
If she needed an appendectomy
如果他要做阑尾切除手术
you'd need my signature for surgery, right?
你必须要有我的签名，对吗？
Therapy is different.
手术是不一样的
Yeah, but this whole--
是的，但这整件事--
None of this makes sense to me.
都让人无法理解
And I'm really starting to--
而且我真的开始--
What's going on?
怎么了？
I cannot stop thinking about it.
我无法停止想这件事
I'm driving my car
开车的时候
whatever, in the office, in a meeting
不管做什么，在办公室，在开会
and I think about him on top of her.
脑子里全是女儿被他欺负的画面
The other night I had this dream. I'd got him.
有天晚上我做梦梦到，我抓到他了
I was beating the life out of him.
我正把他往死里打
I was on top of him and I was punching him
把他放倒狠狠的修理他
and punching him and his face was caving in
我用拳头往死里打他，他的脸被我打的凹陷下去
there was blood going everywhere
到处是血
and I could actually taste it.
甚至我能尝到血的味道
I woke up, I found I'd actually chewed the inside of my mouth.
醒来后，发现咬破了自己的嘴唇
It's my own blood I was tasting.
尝到的血腥味原来是自己的
What if they did catch him and they put him in jail him. How would that make you feel?
如果他们抓到他，把他关进监狱，你会觉得怎样？
Good. Relieved.
那很好，会松一口气
Angry.
生气
Why angry?
为什么生气？
Because I'd still want to rip
因为我仍想把他的脑袋
his fucking head off and now I couldn't.
给拧下来，所以那会让我失望
What else are you angry about?
你还生什么气？
I'm angry I didn't know what was going on.
因为我不知道到底他妈的发生了什么
I'm angry that Annie lied to me.
也不能理解安妮对我说谎
That I didn't know the extent of her intimacy with him.
我就像个白痴都不知道她跟他到底亲密到什么程度
That I couldn't--
气我无法--
What?
什么？
Stop it?
阻止这件事？
We can't control what happens to us or our loved ones.
我们无法控制那些发生在我们和所爱的人身上的事
What happens when Annie goes to college?
安妮上了大学又该怎么办？
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
People get hurt.
人总会受伤
There's only so much we can do
我们能为自己和孩子做的
to protect ourselves, our children.
只是尽力去保护 我们的孩子们
The only thing we can do
我们唯一能做的
is we can be there for each other
是我们可以彼此支持
when we do fall down, to pick each other up.
在跌倒时，互相扶持着站起来
Ugh!
啊！
(man) Can I help you with anything today, sir?
需要我帮忙吗，先生？
(Peter) Hey, Pop!
嗨，爸！
(Will) Hey.
嗨
(Peter)You look older.
你看起来好像老了
(Will) It's only been six weeks, smart ass.
才过了六个星期，少假惺惺
(Peter) Yeah, still, maybe it's, uh
是啊，但，也可能是，呃
like Einstein's special relativity.
像爱因斯坦的狭义相对论
You know, six weeks to me, five years to you.
你知道，我的六周，对你却是五年
(Will) I think I preferred you with a high school education.
我讨厌你变这么聪明
(Peter) Dude. No way. I don't want you to hurt yourself.
不，不行 我可不想你伤了自己
So how was the ride in?
路上还顺利吧？
Okay.
还好
Okay. I'm still a little, ech.
还好，不过我还是有点恶心
Oh. Big night, eh?
噢 通宵达旦，是吧？
I was off my face, wasn't I?
我看起来无精打采，不是吗?
Come here.
过来
Jesus, Pop. What is it?
天啊，爸 到底怎么了？
(Aunt) Where are the kids?
孩子们呢？
(Lynn) Come on, kids. Hurry up, the food 's gonna be cold.
过来，孩子们 快点，菜都快凉了
(Peter)All right, ready?
好吧，准备好了吗？
Hey!
嘿！
it's fantastic.
真棒
(Lynn) Look at the toilet seat cover.
看看这马桶坐垫
It was her idea.
这是她的注意
Let me help you off with your flippers so you can eat.
让我帮你把鸭蹼摘掉才好吃饭
(Kate)No, Mom, that's cheating.
不，妈妈，那是作弊
That's not a very scary mask, Pete.
这面具根本不够吓人，彼得.
It is to Grandpa.
可把爷爷给吓到了
Don't get me started.
别跟我说这个
He's a socialist.
他就是个流氓
(Grandmother) Oh, Cal, now come on.
噢，Cal,快吃吧
No costume, Annie?
不装扮一下吗，安妮？
This is my costume.
这就是我的装扮
(Kate) You're not supposed to wear a penguin
你不能只穿有企鹅的衣服
you're supposed to be a penguin.
而要装扮成企鹅
Do you want me to come or not?
那你要不要我来啊？
Okay. I guess you can come.
好吧 我想你可以来
(Peter) I'm sorry I didn't get to email much.
很抱歉没能常给你发邮件
You know, things have been really crazy.
你知道，事情一团乱都疯了
It's no big deal.
没关系的
No. No, I should have called more. Checked in a bit.
不，不，我应该多打电话给你 关心一下的
You know I love you, right? Right?
你知道我爱你，对吗？对吗？
(Grandmother) Did you kids ever hear the story
孩子们你们有没有听过
about when Grandpa and I met on Halloween?
我和你们爷爷在万圣节认识的故事吗？
He asked me to take a picture of him
他让我给他拍张照片
next to this statue of a werewolf
在这个狼人雕像的旁边
They've all heard the story, Susan.
他们都听过这个故事了，Susan
(Lynn) No, no, we haven 't.
不，不，我们没有
Okay, good.
好的，很好
So, he goes up
所以，他走上前
and he stands right under it
就站在雕像的下面
trying to impress me, of course.
当然，是想让我留下深刻的印象
But it turns out it's just a guy in a costume, right, hon?
结果那个雕像是一个人装扮的，对吗，亲爱的?
[chuckling] And he grabs Grandpa.
然后他抓住爷爷
And Grandpa starts screamin ' like a girl.
爷爷就像小姑娘一样尖叫起来
- (Grandfather) I did not. - (Grandmother) You did.
-我没有 -你有
Annie, honey. Is that corn cold?
安妮,宝贝，那个玉米凉了吗？
Because I could heat it up for you, sweetie.
我可以帮你热一下，宝贝
Mm. it's fine.
嗯 不用
Annie, you have to try the sweet potatoes. They are amazing.
安妮,你得尝尝这些甜土豆 很好吃
Oh, they are, sweetheart, they are. Just, just have a little. You'll love em
噢，是的，宝贝，很好吃 尝一点吧 你会喜欢的
You guys wanna cut my steak, too?
你们是不是牛排也要帮我切好？
So, I hear you got a girl, Pete.
对了，我听说你有女朋友了，彼得.
What? No. No, God, no.
什么？没，没，天啊，这个真没有
No, it's just this girl I met at a mixer.
没有，就是个我在调音室认识的女孩
Yeah, she's a DG.
哦，她是搞唱片的
But we 're not-- you know, we 're just friends.
但我们不是.....只是普通朋友而已
She's super athletic though. She plays tennis and lacrosse.
不过她运动方面很强 她会打网球和曲棍球
You'd really like her.
你会很喜欢她的
Cool.
酷
But, you know, she's, she's not my girlfriend or anything.
但是，你知道，她，她不是我的女朋友什么的
We just started hanging out.
我们才刚开始约会
(Grandfather) Yeah.
哦
Peter, it's okay for you to have a girlfriend.
彼得,你有个女朋友太好了
It's pretty normal. Right, Dad?
这很正常，对吗，爸爸？
I'm not sure I understand.
我不是很明白
You don't understand?
你不明白？
Have you guys had sex yet?
你们发生关系了么？
Annie.
安妮
Was she good?
她厉不厉害？
That's enough.
够了
(Annie) What?
怎么了？
You can tell everybody about my life
你可以把我得生活告诉每个人
about me having sex and who with, but I can't ask him?
可以说我和谁上床，我却不可以问他？
I asked you not to tell him.
我和你说过不要告诉他
That's the only thing I asked.
那是我唯一的要求
Thank you, Dad.
谢谢你，爸爸
I hope you guys have an awesome time.
你们慢慢吃吧
(Lynn) Honey, please, please stay.
宝贝，拜托，拜托留下
(Annie) No. No. Let me go.
不，不，让我走
(Doug) Okay. Good news.
好，好消息
We ran the DNA from his shirt
我们验了他衬衫上的DNA
through the national database.
通过和国家DNA数据库对比
And we actually found a match.
找到了相匹配的DNA
That's, that's incredible.
这，这真是难以置信
So what happens now? You arrest him?
那现在怎么样？抓到他了吗？
(Doug) It's not that easy.
没那么简单
While the DNA is on the database
就算他的DNA在数据库中
it's still a John Doe- We don't know who it belongs to.
也只是属于某个人的-我们并不知道那个人是谁
I don't understand.
我不明白
Well, there were other cases, Will
还有其它类似的案件，威尔
three of them, where rapes were reported.
有三起，都是强奸案
We were able to recover genetic material
我们从受害者和作案现场
from the victim and the crime scene.
都采集到了基因材料
The DNA profile is the same.
DNA检测结果都属于同一个人
It's just that we don't know who it belongs to.
但我们并不知道这个人是谁
So he's done this before.
也就是说他是惯犯
- Yes, he has. - (Lynn) Oh, my God.
-是的，没错 -噢，我的天
Well, he's had other girlfriends before. I told you that.
他以前有过其他女朋友 我跟你说过
These weren't girlfriends, Annie.
她们不是女朋友，安妮.
These were minors who reported a rape.
是报案被强奸的未成年人
Well, DNA can be wrong.
好吧，DNA也可能有错
The odds of these four samples not coming from the same person
这四个样本不是来自同一个人的概率
are in the hundreds of millions. It's the same guy.
只有万分之一，证明这是一个人干的
Now, look. We, uh, we don't normally do this.
你们看，呃，我们一般不这样做
We 're very careful with victim information.
我们要小心保护受害人的信息
But I'm hoping there might be some kind
但是我认为在你们四个女孩之间
of connection between all four of you girls.
或许有些共同点
Maybe you went to the same camp together
可能参加过同一次露营
you shopped at the same mall.
在同一个商场买过东西
I can't give you their names but I was hoping that
我不能说出她们的名字，但我希望
you might take a look at their pictures.
你可以看看她们的照片
(Lynn) Wait a minute. I don't know if this is a good idea.
等等，我不知道这是不是个好主意
No, no. I want, I want to. Yeah.
不，不 我想，我想看看
All right, Annie, do you know this girl?
好吧，安妮,你认识这个女孩吗？
She's from Cleveland.
她来自克利夫兰
She's fifteen years old.
15岁
No.
不认识
No? Okay.
不认识？好的
This is the Milwaukee case.
这是密尔沃基的案子
This photo was taken about a year ago.
这张照片是一年前拍的
She's fourteen.
她14岁
Now, this girl was assaulted in St. Louis seven months ago.
这个女孩七个月前在圣路易斯被强奸了
She's twelve.
她12岁
(Lynn) Oh, my God.
噢，我的天
(Annie) I don't, I don't know them.
我不，我不认识她们
(Doug) Okay. It's okay. You did a good job.
好的 没关系，你做得很好
Thank you, Annie.
谢谢你，安妮
Honey.
宝贝
(Annie) No. I'm fine. I just need a second.
没事 我很好 我只是需要冷静一下
So you're telling me the FBI's been chasing this guy for years?
你是说联邦调查局已经追踪这个家伙好几年了？
It looks that way, yeah.
看来是这样，是的
Look, on the upside, Will there's more information for us.
从另一方面来说，威尔，我们得到了更多的信息
There's more evidence for us.
也有更多的证据
The investigation is seeing a real breakthrough.
调查很快就会有实质性的突破
I bet the agent in St. Louis said the same thing
我打赌7个月前圣路易斯的探员曾说过类似的事
to some family about seven months ago.
也跟受害者的家人也说了同样的话
I understand your frustration, Will, I do
我明白你现在有多难过，威尔，真的
but I'm working as hard as I can for Annie.
但我也在尽力帮助安妮
Yeah, but it's not enough, is it?
是的，但还不够，是吧？
I mean, that sick fuck is still out there grooming other girls, right?
我是说，那个恶心的变态还逍遥法外在引诱其他女孩子，对吗？
Will, I'm doing all I can. I'm sorry you don't see it that way.
威尔,我正在尽力调查，非常遗憾没能让你看到任何进展
(Lynn)Annie ? Annie!
安妮？安妮！
Did she come down here?
她有下来吗？
(Gail)You okay?
你没事吧？
You want something to drink? Water?
你想喝点什么吗？喝点水？
There were other girls.
还有其他的女生
What other girls? Tell me what you mean.
什么其他的女生？你想说什么
Charlie. He had other girls.
查理，他还有其他的女孩
Three of them. Like me.
她们三个，跟我一样
There were other victims, you mean?
你是说还有其他的受害者？
He said that I was special.
他说过我很特别
That I was the only one for him.
说我是他的唯一
But if there are other girls--
但是如果有其他的女孩--
They weren't even-- They weren't even that pretty!
她们甚至都--甚至都没那么漂亮！
Tell me why it matters.
告诉我这有什么关系
No. No. No.
不 不 不
Why does that matter?
这有什么关系？
Because they were just like me.
因为她们跟我很像
He told me, he said I was pretty.
他跟我说，他说我很漂亮
What's wrong with me?
我到底怎么了？
Why does it mean that something 's wrong with you?
这跟你有什么关系呢？
If he lied to me the way he lied to those other girls, he never loved me.
如果他像骗其他女生那样骗我，那他就从来没爱过我
He lied so he could have sex with me.
他只是要骗我和他上床
What, Annie ?
怎么了，安妮？
Oh, my God.
噢，天哪
He raped me.
他强奸了我
He, he raped me.
他，他强奸了我
How could I have been so stupid?
我怎么能那么蠢？
All he wanted-- My God.
他根本只想--我的天啊
All he wanted was--
他只是想--
God, I'm so sorry.
天哪，我好难过
(Lynn) Oh, God. She's finally asleep.
噢，天 她总算睡着了
This guy is one sick fuck.
这个恶心的变态
Will, I'm so worried about her. I've never seen her like this. I'm just--
威尔，我好担心她 我从没见过她这样 我--
He's just destroyed her.
他把她给毁了
He sent her a picture of his dick.
他给她发过他"老二"的照片
Please stop looking at this shit!
别再看这些垃圾了！
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
What the f-- What are you doing?
他妈的 你都在干嘛？
Why are you down here when you should be up there with her?
你本该在楼上陪她，却在这里干嘛？
You think finding this guy is more important
你觉得找出这个家伙更重要吗？
that it's gonna make her better? Do you think that--
那样会让她更好受些吗？难道你觉得--
Well, it might. Or it might save some other poor fucking girl.
也许 或许还可以救到其他可怜的女孩
I want this guy out of my house. I want him out of my house!
我要这个家伙滚出我的家 我要他滚出我们家！
You want me to go up there and talk to her? I've tried.
你要我上去和她谈心？我试过了
She won't fucking talk to me!
她什么都不肯跟我说！
Shut up!
闭嘴！
She finally fell asleep.
她好不容易睡着了
You'd fucking know that if you were up there with her.
你他妈要是在楼上陪着她，你就知道了
It's Annie. It's Annie.
是安妮，她是安妮
She is in pain. She needs you and you're just--
她很痛苦 她需要你的时候你却--
You're sitting there doing nothing!
你却坐在这里什么都没做！
All right.
哦
Here, here you go.[sniffs]
给你，爱干嘛干嘛去
(Coach)Cameron!
卡梅隆！
Look, Vicki's sick. She can't play today.
维琪病了，她今天不能来了
You're gonna start in her place.
你来替她的位置
I don't know, Coach. I--
我不知道，教练 我--
We need you, Annie.
我们需要你，安妮
Can I count on you?
你能胜任吗？
Yeah.
能
That's the spirit.
就是这种精神
(Coach)At the net.
碰网
(Kate)Annie! Harder!
安妮！加油！
(Brit)Hey, guys. Hi, Lynn.
嗨，大家 嗨，琳恩.
(Lynn)Hey.
嘿
You having fun? Yeah?
你玩得开心吗？嗯？
Dig in!
救球！
Nice Set!
打得好！
Block it!
挡住啊！
You having a good time?
你很爽是吗？
Huh?
唔？
You enjoying this, looking at all the young girls?
看着这些年轻女孩，你很爽是吧？
What's that?
你说什么？
You sick fuck!
你这个恶心的变态！
(Will) I'll kill ya! You fucking shit.
我要杀了你！你这个狗日的
(Will) You sick fucking cunt! I'll kill ya!
你个可恶的变态！我要杀了你！
(Lynn) Oh, my God!
噢，我的天哪！
Dad, are you okay?
爸爸，你还好吗？
(Coach) What happened?
发生什么事？
(Lynn) What are you doing?
你在干什么？
(Coach) I'm calling the police.
我去报警
(man) Hey, hey, no, no, there's no need
嘿，嘿，不不，没有必要
it's, it's just a misunderstanding.
只是，只是一点误会
Dad, you're hurt.
爸爸，你受伤了
No, no. Pumpkin, I'm fine, I'm fine. I'm sorry if I scared you, I'm okay.
不，不 宝贝，没事，我很好 抱歉吓到你了，我还好
- (Coach) Are you sure? - (man) Absolutely.
-你确信？ -当然
It's just a misunderstanding, that's all.
只是误会，真没什么
(Coach) Okay, can we get the game going again, please?
那好，可以继续比赛了吗？
How could you do that to me?
你怎能那样对我？
I'm really sorry.
我真的很抱歉
You're sorry? Gee, Dad, thanks.
你很抱歉？噢，爸爸，谢谢
That makes everything so much better.
你说这话可真是太管用了
I lost my temper. I don't know what else to say. I'm sorry.
我失控了 我也不知道该说什么 对不起
Don't you get it? There 's nothing anybody can say.
你还不明白吗？大家都没什么好说的
My life is ruined.
我的生活给毁了
No, it's not ruined.
不，没有
We're going through a tough time but your life's not ruined.
我们会度过这段艰难的时期，你的生活并没有被毁掉
We're going through a tough time?
受煎熬的是我们？
We didn't get raped.
被强奸的不是我们
We're not the laughingstock of New Trier. I am!
新特里尔的笑柄不是我们 是我！(-新特里尔：中学校名)
I got raped. Not you!
被强奸的是我 不是你！
I know that.
我知道
Nothing 's ever gonna be the same.I know that.
我知道，再也无法和从前一样了
But, please, can you please stop reminding me of it every second?
但是求你了，别再时时刻刻提醒我这件事了好吗？
(Brit) Annie, wait! I'm so sorry.
安妮，等等！我真的很抱歉
(Annie) For what? It's not your fault my dad's a psycho.
为什么？你又没有错  是我爸爸神经
What? No. I swear to God, I had nothing to do with it.
什么？不，我对天发誓，我跟这件事一点关系也没有
Wait, what are you talking about?
等下，你在说什么？
The Internet thing.
网上的事啊
What?
什么？
Oh, uh--
噢，呃--
(Brit) Annie!
安妮！
Annie!
Cameron.
卡梅隆
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天
My God.
我的天
[door opens]
Hello?
谁啊？
[steps]
Lynn?
琳恩？
Hello?
喂？
[Iynn, desperate] Will, where have you been? I've been calling you.
威尔,你去哪了？我一直在给你打电话
What, what do you mean? I'm, I'm here. Where are you?
什么，你说什么？我，我在家啊，你在哪？
On my way. ls, is Annie there?
我在路上 Ann，安妮在吗？
No, I don't, why?
不，我不知--怎么了？
Just-- Brittany called me- Something 's happened.
布兰特妮给我打电话--出事了
Is she there?
她在家吗？
What? Annie? What, what happened?
什么？安妮？出，出什么事了？
I-- don't-- just go check, please! Call me back.
我--不知道--快去找找看，快点！记得给我电话
Annie!
安妮！
Annie.
安妮.
Annie, are you in there?
安妮,你在里面吗？
Annie, open this door!
安妮，开门！
Annie!
安妮！
Shit.
天哪
(Lynn) Will?
威尔？
(Will) Call an ambulance!
快叫救护车！
(Will) How many pills have you taken ?
你吃了多少药片？
(Annie) I'm not really--
我真的不--
Call an ambulance!
快叫救护车！
[sobbing]Hello?
喂？
Open your mouth.
张开嘴巴
Open your mouth, sweetheart.
张开嘴巴，亲爱的
(Lynn) We need, please--
我们需要你，求求你--
(Lynn) She's taken too many pills ?
她吃了很多药吗？
Yeah. Come on.
是 再来
It's all right.
没事的
(Will) She asleep?
她睡着了吗？
I'm through talking.
我不想说话
Brittany's spending the night.
布兰特妮今晚陪她睡
Good night.
晚安
(Annie) Dad?
爸爸？
Dad.
爸爸
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
You remember the first time you went in the pool?
还记得你第一次去泳池游泳吗？
What?
什么？
You probably don't. You were two.
你大概不记得了 那时你才两岁
Peter was scared to death the first time he went in.
彼得第一次下水时吓得要死
He screamed and cried so much, he didn't stop.
他不停大喊大叫，叫个不停
He was fine in the bath, but pool...
他在浴缸里没事，但是泳池...
Not you.
你就不一样
You were fearless.
你什么都不怕
I remember.
我记得
You were amazing.
你真叫人吃惊
Came in with me and almost immediately started laughing
跟我下水后你很快就笑了
and playing and splashing around.
然后就开始玩耍，四处泼水
You just had this confidence.
你就是这样的自信
It wasn't just swimming.
不止是游泳
You just had this--
你就是有这种--
trust--in things, people, the world.
信任--信任所有的事，所有的人，和这个世界
It was who you were.
那才是你
No fear.
无所畏惧
God, I loved that.
噢，我喜欢那样
I was so proud of it.
为你感到骄傲
I envied it.
甚至羡慕
And I was so afraid that you'd lose it as you grew up.
我好担心 随着长大你会失去它
That confidence. That faith.
那种信心 那种信念
But you didn't.
但你没有
And then I failed you.
可我却辜负了你
It was my job to make sure you didn't lose it.
守护你是我的职责
To keep you safe.
保护你的安全
What am I if I can't protect you?
如果我都不能保护你，那我算是什么？
And to see you lose that confidence
看着你失去那种自信
to see you question yourself.
看着你质疑自己
That the idea would even occur to you
甚至你还想到
to want to hurt yourself.
要去伤害自己
Or for you to think for one minute
甚至觉得自己不再那么美丽无瑕--
that you weren't as beautiful--
哪怕只是一闪而过的念头
I don't know if you can ever forgive me, Annie.
不知道你会不会原谅我，安妮
I really don't know if you should.
真不知道你是否该原谅
But I'm sorry.
但我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我真的很抱歉
Dad. Daddy.
爸爸，爸爸
I love you so much.
我好爱你
Dad.
爸爸
(boy) Dad. Come on. How much longer?
爸爸，快点啦 还要多久？
(father) We just got here, buddy.
我们才刚到，伙计
Let's at least pick up some stuff for the park. Okay?
逛公园总要准备好东西啊 好吗？
What a day.
多好的日子啊
Susanna- Grab some apples, will ya ?
苏珊娜--拿几个苹果，好吗？
(boy) Hey, Dad. Can I do it for awhile ?
嘿，爸爸 我可以拍一下吗？
Okay. Be careful, all right, buddy?
好，但要小心，知道吗，伙计？
Well, hello. How do I look?
行了，你好 我看去怎样？
Goofy.
哈哈，像傻瓜
Yeah. Probably so.
是啊，也许吧
(Tyler) Mr. Weston!
韦斯顿先生！
Hey, Tyler, how's it going?
嘿，泰勒,你好吗？
I'm good. How about yourself?
我很好 你呢？
I'm good.
我也很好
Uh, Mom, Dad, this is Mr. Weston.
呃，妈妈，爸爸，这位是韦斯顿先生
Hey, very nice to meet you.
嗨，非常高兴认识你们
He's my physics teacher.
他是我的物理老师
Pleasure, pleasure. Hey,Susanna.
幸会，幸会 嘿，苏珊娜
One of my students, Tyler.
我的学生，泰勒.
Oh. Hi, Tyler. I'm Susanna. Nice to meet you.
噢 嗨，泰勒 我是苏珊娜 你好
(Weston) My wife, Susanna.
我爱人，苏珊娜
And I'm Jennifer.
我是珍妮弗
Hi, Jennifer.
嗨，珍妮弗.
And this is our boy, Mark.
这是我们的儿子，马克
(Tyler) Hey, man. How's it goin'?
嘿，伙计，你好吗？
(Weston)So, great day, huh?
嗯，今天天气多好啊，是吧？
(Jennifer) It is gorgeous.
是啊，好极了
感谢欣赏
-=老友影迷公社=-